(Receptionist:)If you have to ask,
maybe you shouldn't be here.
(Sheldon:)I think this is the place.
- Fill these out.
- Thank you.
(Leonard:)- We'll be right back.
- Oh, take your time.
(Receptionist:)I'll just finish my crossword puzzle.
(Receptionist:)Oh, wait.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I don't think I can do this.
(Leonard:)What, are you kidding? You're a semipro.
(Sheldon:)No. We are committing genetic fraud.
There's no guarantee our sperm's
going to generate high-IQ offspring.
(Sheldon:)Think about that.
(Sheldon:)I have a sister with the same basic DNA mix
who hostesses at Fuddruckers.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, this was your idea.
(Leonard:)A little extra money to get
fractional T1 bandwidth in the apartment?
(Sheldon:)I know.
And I do yearn for faster downloads.
(Sheldon:)There's some poor woman
who's gonna pin her hopes on my sperm.
(Sheldon:)What if she winds up with a toddler
who doesn't know if he should use...
...a differential to solve for the area
under a curve?